kenyayote.com 2019-05-18

# Privacy Policy | Kenyayote

When you submit your personal/ **private  ** information to Kenyayote,  you trust us. It is important to understand that we value your privacy and we will not wish to violate it.

Before you read our privacy policies below make sure that you go through our [terms and conditions](https://kenyayote.com/terms/) as they should be read together with our privacy polices.

## **Summary of Our Privacy Policy**

  1. Private information refers to  Credit card, scanned ID,  Financial IDs and financial account numbers, along with passwords.
  2. We will not, rent, lease or sell your Personal/private Information to anybody except when you permit us to do so. Refer to (1.)
  3. We will take reasonable measures to protect and store your private/personal Information from misuse.
  4. Third parties like Google will place ads on kenyayote depending on a users prior visit.
  5. You can opt  out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the Google ads setting. **Learn more on how Google manages data in its ads products in its** [Privacy & Terms web page](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/).
  6.  a) Private information submitted in/on post/page/archive comments and public forums, by you or the public without our knowledge does/do not fall under our Privacy Policy. In this case,  contact +254720680341 or[ fill form here ](https://kenyayote.com/contact/)for action to be taken.

b) Private/personal information (1) submitted under scam/con men or women related posts, categories or pages do not fall under our privacy policy.

## **Our Complete Privacy Policy**

## **Who we are**

Our website address is: [https://kenyayote.com](https://kenyayote.com/)  a brand of Kyote Internet Group Limited.

## **What personal data we collect and why we collect it**

#### 

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

#### **Media**

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

#### **Contact forms**

**Cookies**

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

#### **Embedded content from other websites**

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

#### **Analytics**

** ** Kenyayote.com uses Google analytics to collect visitors data.  Read about Google Analytics privacy policy **<https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html> .** If you want to opt out, [download from this page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) and install the add-on for your web browser

#### 

Third parties like Google will place ads on kenyayote depending a user’s prior visit.  **Learn more on how Google manages data in its ads products in its** [Privacy & Terms web page](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/).

#### **How long we retain your data**

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

#### **What rights you have over your data**

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

#### **Where we send your data**

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

#### **Our contact information**

Contact Elvis Maoro through elvismaoro7@gmail.com for any privacy concerns.

#### **How we protect your data and data breach procedures we have in place**

We have Jetpack WordPress plugin and recently upgraded to premium version to help to protecting our website from any data breach.  Jetpack premium helps in sending a notification instantly incase of any security issues.

**PRIVACY POLICY UPDATED** on 23rd May 2018 to comply with GDPR, [EU user consent policy](https://www.google.com/about/company/consentstaging.html)

 **Do not miss our News Updates:[Subscribe Now](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCElGzZwGl6yFR8Lx9uixWew?sub_confirmation=1)
* **You need an instant unsecured soft loan via mpesa?:[Check our Loan Page Here](https://kenyayote.com/instant-soft-loans-in-kenya-how-to-apply-online-for-mobile-unsecured-loans/) **
* ****Download Teachers CBC schemes of work for PP1, PP2, Grade 1, 2 and 3 From:[Muthurwa.com](https://muthurwa.com/download-cbc-schemes-of-work-for-grade-1-2-3-and-pp1-pp2-new-curriculum/) ****
* ******Looking for High School Teaching and Revision Notes? Check:[High School Notes](https://muthurwa.com/product-category/class-notes/) ******
* ********Have you heard of Muthurwa.com? This is a youths platfom where you can make a living online in kenya through selling your Class notes, templates, ebooks, Wordpress Themes, photos, past papers, tutorials, Business plans, Recipes, House Plans, Magazines, Plugins, Audios, Design services e.t.c Just create your account, upload your product and withdraw your sales earnings to mpesa anytime. You can also make money through referring customers to Muthurwa.com:[Learn How this works](https://muthurwa.com/start-selling/) ********
**

****************** ******************
